One, do not ask about any grievance.
Two, do not ask about death.
It's no use...let go...
Hang in there, Davis...
Geez!
What's wrong with you?
Don't look so scared.
Did you have a nightmare?
I just woke up and saw your face up close.
Of course I'm scared.
Was my face dirty?
I'll bring a girl home and scare you.
What is this?
I asked Uncle Kim to check
your luck with romance.
He said you'll have bad luck this year.
Your room is also in the "illness state".
Uncle Kim told me to display something
made of metal
and can make a sound to dispel
your misfortune.
Don't make me listen to the sutras.
What if you stop the bad luck,
but I end up in a monastery?
Listen, bad luck with romance is not a joke.
It can be quite serious, OK?
My bad luck with romance is over.
Romance to me is a fleeting cloud.
You'll be my only sweetheart, OK?
I'm only getting old.
You're divorced. Don't sound like
it's no big deal.
I thought once you got married,
someone can look after you.
Then I can enjoy a life of leisure.
But in less than a year,
you got a divorce and moved back home.
I thought you'd give me a grandchild,
But it was only my wishful thinking.
This is driving me mad.
I don't know what to do.
Chow time!
Congee with preserved egg and pork! Great!
It tastes different!
Why? You don't like it?
Not exactly. Nice to have a change.
Just tell me if you don't like it.
I won't make it again.
Don't say that.
I'll eat anything you make, Mom.
I need to go...
Wait...
More amulets for bad romance?
For evil spirits.
To ensure you're safe and things go well.
Keep it on you.
OK...
I had things to do tonight.
No dinner for me.
Bye!
In doing the design, I took into
consideration the owner's preferences.
On this wall that is purposely left blank,
I added these shelves
for the owner's favorite perfumes,
so that not only is the space
visually relaxed,
the smell is also allowed to precipitate.
Cut! OK!
Davis, when you get to the sofa,
remember to mention the brand.
Sure.
The windowsill looks empty.
You have any props?
They're all here.
Lam, you have real flowers?
Lam-lam.
Angie!
Angie is also a writer.
I have urgent business to take care of.
Angie will take over.
What a coincidence!
You know each other?
Great! Have a nice chat.
I'll go wrap things up.
Sure!
I didn't expect you to fill in.
You got flowers? It's not Valentine's Day.
No, it's a prop.
I studied this flat.
The design is rather stripped back,
before the owner moves in,
it may seem rather empty and plain,
that's why I brought flowers.
Wifey!
Hubby?
You bought flowers?
Blessed are the pompon mums,
they give a new home a warm welcome.
You talk in rhymes now?
Why are you so happy?
I've been trying to fix the flowers
but I still don't like them.
I guess it's a problem with the flowers.
A flat must have real flowers.
But they're so hard to keep.
We'll just keep changing them
to ensure their freshness.
Great!
Be careful!
Thanks.
Thank you for your help.
Or the shoot wouldn't have gone so well.
To teamwork?
We have a crew car, where are you going?
I'll ask them to drop you.
No thanks. At this hour,
it's easier for me to leave on my own.
Right...at this hour,
you should be at your hang out, the bar.
It gives me inspiration.
Yup, pretty girls are inspirational.
It's good to relax.
Go ahead. I still have work to do.
You need to relax too.
Don't be so uptight about work.
I'm going. Bye!
Bye!
Hey, where were we?
Where's Pi? Just you?
Exactly!
He came out of the men's room
and went back inside.
Why? Weak kidneys?
Is he OK?
He's with a girl.
That girl over there also needs help
to the toilet.
Here's your chance.
Hi...what do you think of this place?
The designer should have good taste.
I find it a bit stuffy.
Why don't we go somewhere else?
I'm quite happy with the ventilation.
Feel free to leave.
Such a waste, pal!
Your wife used to hold you back.
Now? That's a crime to give up
a chance like that.
I came here to catch my breath, not to eat.
You must eat something you feel like eating.
Quality, OK?
Don't eat anything out of convenience.
Set some criteria.
Right...he likes home cooking.
He doesn't want MSG.
Something of a hipster?
Davis, thanks for the renovation.
This set of shooters is on the house.
I designed it based on the theme.
Grab one, don't just stand there.
Great...
Thank you...
Cheers!
Not bad...
Nice!
What? Not again!
No way, it's impossible...
What's going on?
That's Sylvia Siu Zi-yiu. She's a hit.
Another one...
I saw her on TV. She's the promising witch.
She's always livestreaming or go on TV.
More importantly, she's pretty.
After the renovation, I hired her
as a resident guest.
It's a gimmick to draw in the crowd.
Take your pick. I don't believe
you can guess it right every time.
It's responding...
Is it possible?
Let's see...
She's right again...awesome!
We're almost out of booze.
If you want to play another game,
pop another bottle.
No way. You must have fixed it.
How could you guess the highest card
every time?
Sir, if you can't hold your alcohol,
don't force yourself to drink.
Not that I don't want to drink,
I want you to drink with me.
You can't hold your alcohol,
you also can't hold your temper.
What do you mean, you bloody witch?
Would you believe you can't
leave here alive?
What are you doing? Interfering?
Chill, pal!
This chic knows black magic.
Last time I pissed her off...
You should go.
For you.
Thanks.
As a psychic, you know black magic?
Why do you ask?
I told that guy you know black magic.
I pissed you off before,
now I lose all my bets,
I have sleep paralysis every night,
I can't walk straight
and was plagued with hidden diseases.
Like what?
That's the second question.
You need to satisfy my request first.
For your first request,
I assume you like to drink.
But your second request of taking me home,
don't tell me you're a stalker.
I am...afraid that guy would come back
to give you trouble.
That's why I'm following you
and protecting you.
You live here?
This is where I live and give people advice.
Are you interested in coming up
and be my bodyguard?
I am, but a shifu told me I have
bad luck with romance.
You're such a pretty girl,
I'm afraid such close contact
may land me in trouble.
Thanks.
Pretty girls may have nothing to do
with your romance.
You may have the luck of dispelling
a disaster.
Give me a hair.
To perform black magic?
To get your undying devotion.
Shifu was right...
I'm in trouble?
You will repeatedly run into a girl
who has great affinity with you.
It's likely...she's the one who will
go through thick and thin with you.
How do I know who is the right girl for me?
Golden sun, snow in May and burning sky
are signs you'll see when
the right girl shows up.
Golden sun...
Are you OK?
I'm tired.
Maybe you should go.
Are you sure you're OK?
Subscribe to my channel.
I'm fine if you see new updates.
OK, don't stay up late.
Get some rest. I'm going. Bye!
Bye!
I'm so happy to do this livestreaming
for all of you today.
Don't complain Yan Piggy doesn't
take care of her fans.
I came here with my bestie for a massage
and I'm still livestreaming.
This is what Yan Piggy usually wears.
It's very simple, right?
Excuse me, not so hard.
Wow! Thank you, Yan simp for
sending the golden rocket.
It's so cool and Yan Piggy loves it.
But most, most, most importantly,
remember to comment, like and share. Bye!
Thank you.
Hey, Missie, you work in the morning,
and livestream at night,
even while you're enjoying a massage.
Are you really that busy?
You don't understand the fans.
They want to see their idol play video games
as well as how she lives a normal life.
You had the filter on,
how can they see the normal you?
Not everyone is a natural beauty
like you, Miss Man Nga-kei.
You're coming with me to buy a uniform.
Again? You have so many already.
There are all types of nurses.
Even cats are either black or white.
Yan Piggy's best outfit is always
the next one.
Since Yan Piggy has everything all set up,
Kei Piggy can't say no, right?
How dare you say no?!
Your life used to revolve around
your husband,
and it was impossible to see you.
Now that you're single again,
it's time you dote on me.
Did you know I prefer to stay home
to binge on TV dramas and read?
I can play video games with you,
but I don't want to go out.
But you would go to Hell and back
for you know who.
OK...I'll go. I'll go with you.
I'll go with you later...
Great!
Wear it with me.
I'll help you shop...
What are you looking for?
Tangerine peel.
It's over there.
Hello, son?
Mom, did you send me the wrong address?
I can't find it.
Of course not! Look again.
Do you have to buy your tangerine peel
from that shop?
If you don't want the trouble,
next time I make congee,
you better not complain.
Go look...
When did I complain...?
Auntie!
Oh, Angie!
No need to look again.
You bought it for me?
No, I was shopping with a friend.
It was on the way.
You're so sweet.
That brat is useless.
I gave him the address and he can't find it.
He goes grocery shopping with you
all the time.
He's a good son.
How is he?
He's such a fussy eater.
I used a different tangerine peel
in the congee
and he frowned.
That's why I came here to buy
the one you used.
How are you lately?
The same. Not too bad.
A bit busy because I have a show on air.
Auntie, when you cook,
you can add tangerine peel on anything.
I used to make tea for Davis
and he liked it a lot.
When it comes to cooking,
my hat's off to you.
Hello? No need, I found it...
From the herb store next to the market.
OK...see you at the corner.
(There was a man)
(That sailed the seas)
(He left his woman)
(behind to leave)
(He left his children)
(to mourn alone)
(But don't you cry)
(He's coming home)
Mom, this is the kind...
Last time you said a change of taste.
Now you want more of the same?
Anything you cook will taste good.
What a sweet talker.
Pissed? OK, I'll do the dishes.
Better not. I don't want to lose more bowls.
You better go pack your things.
I only broke a few bowls,
you're throwing me out already?
The suitcase has been sitting there
since you moved back home.
If I didn't touch it for a few months,
that means the things are useless.
Just toss them.
No, they are your things.
Sort them out yourself.
OK...I'll do it.
The design...
(One and a half years ago)
Well? Are you finished?
Wifey, your smile is so stiff.
Try to look more natural.
Who's your wife?
You, sooner or later.
What's wrong with calling you that?
Hurry up, there are people around.
I'm painting. We have nothing to hide.
Don't look so embarrassed.
Hey, it's raining.
Cover it up!
I told you the Observatory predicted
rain for today.
But the maple leaves look their best today.
Luckily, it didn't get wet.
But you're all wet, silly goose!
You're so stuck up,
hanging your paintings on the whole wall.
They're all paintings of you.
You begged me to marry you
because you like my paintings.
What? I begged you?
Of course you did.
You turned things around.
If you didn't beg, why would I propose?
Stop...
The cotton tree wadding slipped
through my hands,
the same hands you held and dropped.
(Sent)
Sylvia!
What's up?
Where are we going?
Sh...don't ask.
(Chan Sin To Memorial Primary School)
You know how to use a feng shui compass?
You know eastern and western
fortune telling.
All things have a spiritual essence
and are inter-related.
The world is big
and there's so much we don't know.
I always study things that seem interesting.
What's that?
This magnetic field detector
can detect the changes in the
magnetic field around us.
It changes color when it detects
something abnormal.
Red means it's nearby.
We're looking for spirits?
We're doing a field test.
Both your compass and the machine
had a strong reaction.
Does that mean there was something...?
A classroom in Chan Sin To
Memorial Primary School
had an electrical leakage because
the switch was in disrepair.
During lunch break, several kids
were hurt from the electric shock.
One of the girls stepped on a plastic ball,
and died from hitting her head
against the wall.
A plastic ball?
The baby doll we just saw was a girl.
It's late now, stepping on the ball
is not unusual.
Dolls are either a boy or a girl.
Who's there? You're not supposed to be here.
Run...
Being chased by humans
is scarier than by a ghost.
Sometimes, humans are scarier than ghosts.
You're pretty even when you're making faces.
It's fitting for tonight's theme.
For our first attempt to seek out a spirit,
we should commemorate it with a post.
Why don't you tag me?
Sylvia Siu Yiu 1111.
OK...done!
Nice picture. Give it a like.
Hey!
What? Who's that?
My ex-wife.
Sorry! Should I unlike it?
No need.
You had a big fight?
No, we split on good terms.
That was three months ago.
But lately, I kept running into her.
Take this picture for instance.
I saw the cotton tree wadding,
got out of the car to take a picture.
I didn't know she was there
and I showed up in her picture.
I remember I didn't see her that day.
There was another time,
I was on a TV show to talk about a design.
She was filling in for my colleague
as a copywriter.
Maybe it's your fate.
It's May now.
Is the cotton tree wadding
considered "snow in May"?
Last time she brought sunflowers
when she filled in for my colleague.
Could that be "golden sun"?
What about "burning sky"?
Will there be a fire next time we meet?
If you don't believe it,
maybe you overlooked something.
What have I overlooked?
"The cotton tree wadding slipped
through my hands,"
"the same hands you held and dropped."
She knew you were in the picture.
By saying that, she's obviously
not yet over you.
She's known to be sensitive.
Maybe she wrote that because
of what's in that picture.
When I saw her recently,
I didn't sense anything.
What about you? Are you over her?
Honestly, she's a good wife.
It was my fault, I'm not cut out
to be a married man.
Marriage is about finding
the right other half.
If things are not over for you,
you are somewhere still connected.
Connected?
We haven't sold the flat we're still
making payments on.
She's still living there.
Is that considered a connection?
Tangible or not, that's still a connection.
Romance and bad luck are often inseparable.
Passionate love, like fireworks,
is dazzling and exciting
but also dangerous.
Ordinary love, like temperature,
is still water that runs deep.
You want fireworks or temperature?
Destiny is often not your choice.
I'll drop you off...
Try to scoop it out in one piece.
We need to steam that later.
Brother On, is this really good?
When I scoop this out, I usually toss it.
You'll soon find out.
Look, Brother On!
What? Hey...
Stop the camera...
Sorry...I didn't mean it!
Bowie, did you scald yourself?
I'm fine.
Be careful...Brother On, I'm sorry,
we may need to do the dish again.
But we need to hand over
the studio in an hour.
The beef stew takes at least two hours.
We have two other dishes to make
according to the rundown.
What can we do?
It's OK. Brother On,
leave the beef stew to me.
Ka-kei, get someone to clean this up.
Sure!
Director, you can film Brother On and Bowie
making the next dish.
Sang and I will take care of
everything else.
Sang, come here...
OK!
Here's the honey...
Thanks, Sang.
Brother On, I love this beef stew.
It's tender and the acidity of the wine
has a hint of sweetness,
giving it complexity.
I'll make other dishes for you next time.
Promise?
See you on the next Gourmet Chef Encore.
Bye!
Cut! Good take!
OK...thank you.
You're a good cook for someone so young!
Thanks, Brother On!
She truly rose to the occasion.
Without you, I wouldn't know
what to do, Angie.
Yes, thank goodness you were here.
Stop teasing me. I'm the writer,
It's my job to solve problems.
I get paid to do this.
But why did you add honey?
It wasn't on the ingredients list.
Honey contains proteinase
that can make the beef tender
in a short time.
Pineapple juice can do that too.
OK...let's clear out.
Thank you...
Let's pack up...
Angie!
Sesame paste and sweet potato soup?
Nobody knows me better than you,
Yip Lai-yan.
You bet!
Angie, let's go see the flame trees
and have a picnic.
That looks gorgeous!
But I'm really busy lately.
I may not make it, sorry!
I know, only Davis is king.
Says who?
You couldn't stop smiling
when he liked your picture.
You're still in love with Davis.
Even the picture you post
had him in the background.
I admit I'm still in love with him.
Just learn to let go...
(Delete)
What are you doing?
Chopping down the tree.
See? Look at the other beautiful
trees waiting for you.
I'll invite other good catches for you.
You must show up.
On today's live cast, I'll show you
how to make a romance orgonite pyramid.
The key to making the pyramid
is how to distribute the crystals.
Next, you add UV gel
and put it under the lamp
for about five to six minutes.
You can also add natural ingredients,
such as the petals from the
blooming flame trees.
Then this person will be thinking of you
at all times.
I heard the flame trees in
Lam Shing Country Park are gorgeous.
Off I go!
Angie, where are you going?
Lam Shing Country Park.
I saw on the news the flame trees
are in full bloom.
What a coincidence! I'm heading out there.
Hop in. I'll give you a lift.
OK.
Seat belt.
Is everything OK with you lately?
OK!
Shall we go look?
Sure!
Angie!
What a coincidence, Davis!
We found the perfect spot...
We brought food. Want to join us?
No thanks. I'll walk around by myself.
OK!
Let's go!
Bye!
Angie, want something to drink?
Thanks.
Liz said you're a writer for the TV station
and you also do research.
What programs are you working on?
Just finished a cooking show
and looking for new ideas right now.
How about a dating reality show?
It's a big hit nowadays.
Something like Romance Hit & Run,
or Living Under the Same Roof.
The name tells you what kind of
program it is
and will catch eyeballs for sure.
What do you think?
Good idea!
Excuse me, I need to use the toilet.
OK.
Now she's on the run.
(There was a man)
(That sailed the seas)
(He left his woman)
(behind to leave)
Golden sun, snow in May and burning sky
are signs you'll see when
the right girl shows up.
This is the prettiest of all the trees.
Yeah. The canopy is so big
it looks like the sky is on fire.
Too bad, I don't have a model today.
What kind of pose do you want?
You're actually my perfect model.
If we were not married,
I'm sure we'll make a good team.
It's raining!
It's just a light drizzle.
The painting will get wet.
Leave it, Angie!
Angie...
Davis...
It's no use, let go...
Hang in there...
Remember when we first got married,
Mother drew a lot for us?
It says if we don't give up,
we'll always land on our feet.
Hang in there, Davis...
Davis...
Help!
Davis...wake up...
Help, anyone?
Anyone out there...